Privacy Policy (pomodoro-tracker.com)
-------------------------------------

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. Please read the privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how Pomodoro-Tracker collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the service.

Topics:

#### What data do we collect?

When registering on the service you voluntarily give us information such as your name and email address.

In addition, when you use our service, you give us the consent to use the following data:

* Email Address
* IP Address
* Name and surname (optional, not processed)
* Language preference (optional, not processed)
* Time Zone preference (optional, not processed)
* User Picture (optional, not processed)

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register or use service features in the following ways:

* To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content in which you are most interested.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
* To administer a contest or other service feature.

#### How do we protect your information?

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

#### What are your data protection rights?

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

**The right to access** – You have the right to request us for copies of your personal data. Please note you can do it using the (export CSV).

**The right to rectification** – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete the information you believe is incomplete.

**The right to erasure** – You have the right to erase your personal data, under certain conditions. Please note you can do it using the application's settings.

If you make a request, we have two week to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at our email: [\[email protected\]](https://pomodoro-tracker.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology.

For further information, visit [allaboutcookies.org](https://allaboutcookies.org/).

We uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:

* Keeping you signed in
* Understanding how you use our service

There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:

* Functionality – We use these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

#### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Privacy policies of other websites

The website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.

#### Changes to our privacy policy

We keep the privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page.  
This privacy policy was last updated on 23 July 2020.

Previous versions are available:

#### How to contact us

If you have any questions about the privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Email us at: [\[email protected\]](https://pomodoro-tracker.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Tweet

Share

Pin

Share

Send

Send

[Version 22.0.4](https://pomodoro-tracker.com/news) · [Privacy Policy](https://pomodoro-tracker.com/privacy) · [Terms and Conditions](https://pomodoro-tracker.com/terms) · [Slack Community](https://join.slack.com/t/pomodoro-tracker/shared_invite/zt-6x48sr9v-_M4DPAlcu~huu5rC29kNEA) · © [\[email protected\]](https://pomodoro-tracker.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 2015

Pomodoro-Tracker is not related to the Pomodoro Technique™/Pomodoro™’s trademark holder Cirillo Company and respects its trademarks.  
Pomodoro Technique® and Pomodoro® are registered trademarks of Francesco Cirillo.  
All logos and marks contained herein are the property of their respective owners.
